pixelperfectdigital.com 2005-02-09

# Pixel Perfect Digital : Download free images, textures, backgrounds, illustrations, digital art and stock photos.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

**Information We Collect**  
Pixel Perfect Digital collects the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from ibm.com or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to our site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). Pixel Perfect Digital collects this user information for purposes of site monitoring and product improvement. We do use third-party advertising to serve ads on our site. These companies may use "cookies" to customize the advertising you see based on non-personally identifiable demographic information. This allows us to provide advertisements on this site about goods and services that may be of interest to you.   
**Newsletter**  
We only email our subscribers Pixel Perfect Digital related news and information. We will never share, sell, or rent your email address to any 3rd party. You may unsubscribe from our newsletter anytime by emailing subscriptions@ppdigital.com 

**Guestbook**  
Our guestbook contains fields for you to add Name, email address, and homepage URL. The only place this information is recorded is in the guestbook. You should know that supplying your email address or web page URL on any web page makes that address available to anyone on the Internet. Pixel Perfect Digital takes no responsibility for any unsolicited email you may receive as a result of a 3rd party "harvesting" your email address or URL from our guestbook. The only way to prevent this from happening is to omit this information when you sign ( it isn't required to leave comments ).

**Links**  
Our web sites contain links to other sites. Pixel Perfect Digital is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us by email at privacy@ppdigital.com. 

© 2005 Pixel Perfect Digital, Inc.

Top of Page
